Preliminary Guide to the Federation for American Immigration Reform (FAIR) records, 1867-2006 MS2195
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Subject files, 1974-2006; Series 8
  - General subject files, 1980-2003; Series 8 Subseries 6
    - Border Violence, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 160, Folder 9)
    - Bracero Program, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 205, Folder 13)
    - Braceros, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 205, Folder 12)
    - Brain Drain, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 184, Folder 11)
    - Bribery, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 202, Folder 7)
    - California, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 209, Folder 4)
    - Cancer, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 212, Folder 5)
    - Carrying Capacity, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 201, Folder 17)
    - Cartoons, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 180, Folder 12)
    - Census (The), undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 210, Folder 3)
    - Census Projections, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 211, Folder 2)
    - Census/FAIR Lawsuit [1/2], undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 173, Folder 5)
    - Census/FAIR Lawsuit [2/2], undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 173, Folder 6)
    - Central Americans, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 191, Folder 6)
    - Chain Migration, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 156, Folder 6)
    - Child Labor, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 184, Folder 9)
    - China One-Child, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 156, Folder 3)
    - Chinese Student Protection Act, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 174, Folder 2)
    - Chinese-Americans, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 191, Folder 9)
    - Citizenship, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 198, Folder 8)
    - Clinton and NAFTA, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 205, Folder 9)
    - Colonias, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 209, Folder 9)
    - Compassion Fatigue, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 176, Folder 13)
    - Construction Industry, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 187, Folder 5)
    - Coverage of the Cost Issue, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 207, Folder 10)
    - Crime, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 215, Folder 11)
    - Criminal Aliens 1/3], undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 159, Folder 5)
    - Criminal Aliens [2/3], undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 159, Folder 6)
    - Criminal Aliens [3/3], undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 159, Folder 7)
    - Crowding, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 201, Folder 2)
    - Cuba Democracy Act of '92 [1/2], 1992; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 174, Folder 3)
    - Cuba Democracy Act of '92 [2/2], 1992; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 174, Folder 4)
    - Cuban Americans, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 191, Folder 7)
    - Cuban Exodus '94 [1/2] undated, 1994; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 174, Folder 7)
    - Cuban Exodus '94 [2/2], 1994; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 174, Folder 8)
    - Cuban Rafters, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 163, Folder 2)
    - Cultural Asylum, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 177, Folder 8)
    - Cultural Defense, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 211, Folder 7)
    - Cultural, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 195, Folder 5)
    - Culture Clash, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 211, Folder 6)
    - Culture on the Job, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 184, Folder 6)
    - Current Population Survey(CPS), undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 211, Folder 3)
    - D.O.A., undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 163, Folder 3)
    - Danger on the Job, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 184, Folder 8)
    - [Day Laborers and Agricultural Guest Workers], undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 255, Folder 2)
    - Day Laborers/Esquineros, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 183, Folder 6)
    - Day Laborers/Esquineros, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 183, Folder 7)
    - Deferred Enforced Departure, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 160, Folder 2)
    - Degradation: Air, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 201, Folder 13)
    - Degradation: Energy, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 201, Folder 14)
    - Degradation: Food Supply, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 201, Folder 15)
    - Degradation: Land, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 201, Folder 11)
    - Degradation: Water, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 201, Folder 12)
    - Demographics/Population Shifts, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 200, Folder 2)
    - Dental, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 212, Folder 6)
    - Deportation Hearings, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 164, Folder 9)
    - Deportation ----LIFERS, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 164, Folder 10)
    - Deportation, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 164, Folder 5)
    - Deportation, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 164, Folder 6)
    - [Deporting the Undocumented], 2005; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 256, Folder 11)
    - Deportee Detention, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 164, Folder 7)
    - Deportee Detention, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 164, Folder 8)
    - Discrimination on the Job, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 184, Folder 7)
    - Discrimination, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 211, Folder 8)
    - Diseases, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 212, Folder 1)
    - Displacement [1/2], undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 181, Folder 6)
    - Displacement [2/2], undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 181, Folder 7)
    - Disunity, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 198, Folder 10)
    - Diversity Visa Lottery, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 156, Folder 5)
    - Diversity, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 211, Folder 4)
    - Domestic Policy, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 215, Folder 3)
    - Domestics, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 186, Folder 4)
    - Dorcy Report, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 169, Folder 7)
    - Drywallers, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 187, Folder 6)
    - Dual Nationality/ Dual Citizenship; Mexico [1/2], undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 157, Folder 10)
    - Dual Nationality/ Dual Citizenship; Mexico [2/2], undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 157, Folder 11)
    - E-B 1st Pref. Priority Workers, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 175, Folder 12)
    - E-B 2nd Pref. Exceptionally Able, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 175, Folder 13)
    - E-B 3rd Pref. Skilled Workers, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 176, Folder 1)
    - E-B 4th Pref. Special Immigrants, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 176, Folder 2)
    - E-B 5th Pref. Employment Creation, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 176, Folder 3)
    - Economic Progress of Immigrants, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 184, Folder 3)
    - Economy, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 181, Folder 3)
    - Editorials, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 180, Folder 11)
    - Education, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 192, Folder 10)
    - Education/Skill Level, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 184, Folder 1)
    - Education/Skill Level, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 184, Folder 2)
    - Emigration, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 200, Folder 6)
    - Employer Sanctions [1/2], undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 168, Folder 9)
    - Employer Sanctions [2/2], undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 168, Folder 10)
    - Employment-Based Visas, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 175, Folder 11)
    - Engineering [1/2], undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 185, Folder 6)
    - Engineering [2/2], undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 185, Folder 7)
    - Entrepeneurship, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 184, Folder 4)
    - Entry/Exit System, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 162, Folder 3)
    - Environment (The), undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 202, Folder 11)
    - Environmental Degradation, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 201, Folder 10)
    - Environmental Issues, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 201, Folder 16)
    - ES Busts (Employer Sanctions Busts), undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 169, Folder 1)
    - ES Discrimination, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 169, Folder 4)
    - ES Repeal, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 169, Folder 5)
    - Ethnic Clustering, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 200, Folder 5)
    - Ethnic Groups, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 191, Folder 2)
    - Ethnic Riots, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 199, Folder 5)
    - Ethnic Tension, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 199, Folder 1)
    - Ethnic Tension: LA Riots [1/2], undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 199, Folder 6)
    - Ethnic Tension: LA Riots [2/2], undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 199, Folder 7)
    - Ethnic Tension: Mt. Pleasant Riots, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 199, Folder 8)
    - Ethnic Tension: Washington Heights Riots, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 199, Folder 9)
    - European Asylum, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 156, Folder 2)
    - Exchange Students, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 194, Folder 2)
    - Exclusion, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 160, Folder 3)
    - Expedited Removal, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 160, Folder 6)
    - Extended Voluntary Departure, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 160, Folder 5)
    - External Enforcement, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 163, Folder 4)
    - Family Planning, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 208, Folder 6)
    - Family Violence, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 202, Folder 6)
    - FGM Asylum, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 177, Folder 9)
    - Financial Aid, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 193, Folder 9)
    - Fiscal Effects, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 206, Folder 10)
    - Food Stamps, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 190, Folder 2)
    - Foreign Debt, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 187, Folder 8)
    - Foreign Policy, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 215, Folder 2)
    - Foreign Students [1/2], undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 193, Folder 7)
    - Foreign Students [2/2], undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 193, Folder 8)
    - Foreign Terrorism, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 214, Folder 8)
    - Foreign Terrorism, 1992-1993; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 214, Folder 9)
    - Foreign Terrorism, 1994-1995; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 214, Folder 10)
    - Foreign Terrorism, 1996-1997; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 214, Folder 11)
    - Foreign Terrorism, 1998-1999; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 214, Folder 12)
    - Foreign Trade Treaties, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 187, Folder 10)
    - Foreign Trade, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 187, Folder 9)
    - Gallup Poll, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 179, Folder 3)
    - Garment Industry, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 187, Folder 3)
    - Gay Americans, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 192, Folder 9)
    - Gay Asylum, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 155, Folder 8)
    - Gay Asylum: Asyl- Kasinga, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 155, Folder 7)
    - George W. Bush, Jr. Administration, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 181, Folder 1)
    - Gerrymandering, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 215, Folder 5)
    - Golden Venture, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 174, Folder 6)
    - "Greenhaters", undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 210, Folder 2)
    - Guestworkers, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 183, Folder 2)
    - [H1B], undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 255, Folder 1)
    - H1B Specialty Occupations [1/2], undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 206, Folder 3)
    - H1B Specialty Occupations [2/2], undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 206, Folder 4)
    - H1B: 1998 Cap Battle, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 175, Folder 3)
    - H1B: battle 2000, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 175, Folder 4)
    - [The H1B Straightjacket], 2000; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 256, Folder 6)
    - H2A Agricultural Temporary Workers, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 206, Folder 5)
    - H2B Non-Agricultural Temporary Workers, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 206, Folder 6)
    - Haiti early 90's, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 174, Folder 5)
    - Harbors, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 161, Folder 8)
    - Health Issues, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 211, Folder 12)
    - [Healthcare], undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 255, Folder 8)
    - Healthcare Insurance, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 213, Folder 3)
    - Healthcare Reform, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 212, Folder 10)
    - Healthcare Reform: Illegals, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 212, Folder 11)
    - Healthcare Strain, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 213, Folder 2)
    - Heath Language barriers, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 212, Folder 8)
    - Heathcare Fraud, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 213, Folder 1)
    - Heathcare, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 212, Folder 9)
    - H1A Registered Nurses, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 206, Folder 2)
    - Hispanics, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 191, Folder 3)
    - History -- Elian Gonzalez, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 174, Folder 1)
    - History -- Michigan Ads, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 173, Folder 8)
    - History--- Storm Lake, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 173, Folder 7)
    - History, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 172, Folder 7)
    - History: Post-Colonial Era (1991-present), undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 173, Folder 4)
    - History: Post-Ellis Island Lull (1921-1964), undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 173, Folder 1)
    - History: Pre-Ellis Island (1820-1880), undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 172, Folder 8)
    - History: Ellis Island Period (1880-1920), undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 172, Folder 9)
    - History: The New Wave (1965-1990), undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 173, Folder 2)
    - HIV Asylees, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 156, Folder 10)
    - HIV+/Aids, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 212, Folder 2)
    - Homeland Security, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 213, Folder 7)
    - Horror and Outrage [1/2], undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 181, Folder 4)
    - Horror and Outrage [2/2], undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 181, Folder 5)
    - Hospitals, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 212, Folder 7)
    - Hotel and Restaurant Industry, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 187, Folder 4)
    - Housing, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 201, Folder 3)
    - Housing: Assisted/Public, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 201, Folder 6)
    - Housing: Crowded Housing, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 201, Folder 5)
    - Housing: Demand, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 201, Folder 7)
    - Housing: Effects and Conflicts, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 201, Folder 4)
    - Housing: Ownership, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 201, Folder 8)
    - Huddle, 1993; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 206, Folder 12)
    - Huddle, 1994; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 206, Folder 13)
    - Huddle, 1996; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 207, Folder 1)
    - Huddle, 1999; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 207, Folder 2)
    - Hurricane Mitch, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 175, Folder 2)
    - ID Fraud [1/2], undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 169, Folder 2)
    - ID Fraud [2/2], undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 169, Folder 3)
    - ID Fraud, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 204, Folder 3)
    - ID: Birth/Death Certificates, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 203, Folder 3)
    - ID: Bordercard, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 203, Folder 5)
    - ID: Drivers License [1/2], undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 170, Folder 1)
    - ID: Drivers License [2/2], undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 170, Folder 2)
    - ID: Green Cards, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 203, Folder 4)
    - ID: Passports, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 169, Folder 9)
    - ID: Social Security Card, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 203, Folder 6)
    - ID: Verification Systems, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 203, Folder 7)
    - IDENT, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 168, Folder 8)
    - Identification, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 169, Folder 8)
    - IHP/Local Cooperation [1/3], undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 168, Folder 4)
    - IHP/Local Cooperation [2/3], undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 168, Folder 5)
    - IHP/Local Cooperation [3/3], undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 168, Folder 6)
    - Illegal Aliens: Profiles and Estimates, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 159, Folder 1)
    - Illegal Immigration [1/2], undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 158, Folder 13)
    - Illegal Immigration [2/2], undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 158, Folder 14)
    - Imm./Environment Connection, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 210, Folder 1)
    - Immediate Relatives Category, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 175, Folder 7)
    - Immigrant Education, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 192, Folder 11)
    - Immigrants v. Blacks, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 199, Folder 4)
    - Immigrants v. Immigrants, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 199, Folder 3)
    - Immigrants v. Natives, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 199, Folder 2)
    - Immigration Education, College, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 193, Folder 5)
    - Immigration Education, Graduate School, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 193, Folder 6)
    - Immigration Education, K-12 [1/3], undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 193, Folder 1)
    - Immigration Education, K-12 [2/3], undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 193, Folder 2)
    - Immigration Education, K-12 [3/3], undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 193, Folder 3)
    - Immigration Reform, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 158, Folder 2)
    - Income Disparity, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 182, Folder 5)
    - Income Inequality, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 190, Folder 3)
    - Indian-Americans, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 192, Folder 3)
    - Industry and Trade, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 184, Folder 14)
    - Information Technology Industry [1/2], undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 186, Folder 2)
    - Information Technology Industry [2/2], undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 186, Folder 3)
    - Inmate Deportation, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 160, Folder 1)
    - Inspections, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 164, Folder 3)
    - In-State Tuition, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 194, Folder 1)
    - Interdiction, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 164, Folder 4)
    - Internal Enforcement, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 168, Folder 1)
    - International Conference on the Migrant, 2007; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 256, Folder 2)
    - International Polls, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 179, Folder 1)
    - Internationalism/Globalism, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 198, Folder 12)
    - Investigations, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 168, Folder 2)
    - IRCA Amnesty: SLIAG, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 204, Folder 7)
    - J1 Visas / Foreign Exchange, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 158, Folder 10)
    - Japanese-Americans, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 192, Folder 1)
    - Jewish Americans, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 192, Folder 6)
    - Job Magnet, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 184, Folder 12)
    - Koreans-Americans, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 191, Folder 10)
    - Kosovo Crisis, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 178, Folder 2)
    - Labor Market Effects, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 182, Folder 1)
    - Labor Supply, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 182, Folder 10)
    - Labor Certification, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 169, Folder 6)
    - Labor Supply: Labor Certification, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 183, Folder 8)
    - Labor Unions, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 187, Folder 7)
    - Language Barriers, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 195, Folder 2)
    - Language Conflict, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 195, Folder 3)
    - Language in the Government, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 195, Folder 4)
    - Language on the Job, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 184, Folder 10)
    - Language [1/2], undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 194, Folder 11)
    - Language [2/2], undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 195, Folder 1)
    - Latino National Political Survey, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 179, Folder 5)
    - Lau v. Nichols, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 194, Folder 7)
    - [Legal and Illegal Immigrant Population], undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 255, Folder 3)
    - Legal Aliens, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 175, Folder 5)
    - Limits/Caps, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 158, Folder 3)
    - Local Costs, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 207, Folder 6)
    - LoweCase '98, 1998; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 178, Folder 1)
    - Mafias/Organization Crime, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 215, Folder 2)
    - Maids, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 186, Folder 7)
    - Mail-Order Brides, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 175, Folder 9)
    - Malthusianism, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 202, Folder 5)
    - Mariel Boatlift, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 173, Folder 3)
    - Maquiladoras, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 205, Folder 11)
    - Meat and Poultry Processing [1/2], undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 187, Folder 1)
    - Meat and Poultry Processing [2/2], undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 187, Folder 2)
    - Media Opinion, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 180, Folder 10)
    - Medical Industry, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 184, Folder 16)
    - Medical Requirements, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 156, Folder 8)
    - Medical Requirements: HIV, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 156, Folder 9)
    - Merit/Point System, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 158, Folder 5)
    - Mexican-Americans, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 191, Folder 4)
    - [The Mexican Migrant Guide], undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 256, Folder 1)
    - Mexico versus the U.S., undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 161, Folder 4)
    - Midwives, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 185, Folder 1)
    - Migrant Labor [1/3], undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 183, Folder 3)
    - Migrant Labor [2/3], undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 183, Folder 4)
    - Migrant Labor [3/3], undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 183, Folder 5)
    - Moratorium, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 158, Folder 4)
    - Motor-Voter, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 215, Folder 7)
    - Multicultural Education, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 194, Folder 9)
    - Multiculturalisim, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 211, Folder 5)
    - Murder and Mayhem, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 202, Folder 9)
    - Muslim Americans, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 192, Folder 7)
    - NAFTA, 1991; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 188, Folder 2)
    - NAFTA, 1992; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 188, Folder 3)
    - NAFTA, 1993; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 188, Folder 4)
    - NAFTA Con, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 205, Folder 8)
    - NAFTA Pro, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 205, Folder 7)
    - NAFTA, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 188, Folder 1)
    - Nannies, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 186, Folder 6)
    - Narcotics/Drug Smuggling, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 216, Folder 4)
    - National Cost Estimates, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 206, Folder 11)
    - National Cost Estimates: FAIR Studies, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 207, Folder 4)
    - National Cost Estimates: RAND Studies, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 207, Folder 3)
    - National ID Card, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 204, Folder 4)
    - National Polls, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 179, Folder 2)
    - National Security [1/2], undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 213, Folder 4)
    - National Security [2/2], undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 213, Folder 5)
    - Native Terrorism, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 214, Folder 7)
    - Naturalization Backlog, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 157, Folder 1)
    - Naturalization Fees, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 157, Folder 5)
    - Naturalization Rates, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 157, Folder 8)
    - Naturalization Requirements, undated; Series 8 Subseries 6 (Box 157, Folder 2)